(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Hello.
(Girl:)So, what are you supposed to be?
(Leonard:)Me?
(Sheldon:)I'll give you a hint.
Vroom.
(Girl:)A choo-choo train?
(Leonard:)Close.
Vroom.
A brain-damaged choo-choo train?
(Sheldon:)How wasted am I?
Dancing all by myself
Cannot control the beat
When you make me weak
Vroom.
[UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF GIANTS'
"MAMA'S ROOM" PLAYS ON STEREO]
(Girl:)I still don't get it.
(Sheldon:)I'm the Doppler effect.
(Girl:)Okay, if that is some sort
of learning disability...
(Girl:)...I think it's very insensitive.
(Leonard:)Why don't you just tell people
you're a zebra?
you're one of the seven dwarves?
(Leonard:)Because I'm Frodo.
(Sheldon:)Yes, well, I'm the Doppler effect.
- Oh, no.
- What?
(Leonard:)That's Penny's ex-boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)What do you suppose he's doing here?